<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">turistiandov2</string>
    <string name="resenahoteles">In San Jeronimo you will find many and diverse kinds of hotels, luxurious and cheap, as well as hotels famous for their great lodging comfort.
    Here you can find hotels from 5,000 Colombian pesos per night to 1,000,000 Colombian pesos per night, themes and special events in each hotel
    clearly improving its quality the higher the price, do you want to know more?, continue and you will find more information about them.</string>
    <string name="resenarestaurantes">In San Jeronimo we have excellent service, very rich food, a pleasant and fresh place. very familiar atmosphere and quality food
    cheap prices and almost in any restaurant you can find your typical food the delicious black pudding, we have a variety of food, you will find many quality places
    where to have breakfast, lunch and dinner, but if you are one of those who love fast food here you will find quality places with very generous portions
    and at an excellent price.</string>
    <string name="resenaturismo">In San Jeronimo you will never get bored, you will always have things to do, Places to see, ways to travel and outstanding experiences,
    visit the tamarindos park, or the kanaloa water park, or if you are more extreme you could go paragliding, see the bike junkies or go to the museum, there are thousands of things to do
    the limit is your imagination, creativity or boredom.</string>
    <string name="opcion1">English</string>
    <string name="opcion2">Italian</string>
    <string name="opcion3">Spanish</string>
    <string name="opcion4">About us</string>

    <string name="usuario">name</string>
    <string name="contraseña">password</string>
    <string name="ingresar">enter</string>
    <string name="hoteles">hotel</string>
    <string name="restaurante">restaurant</string>
    <string name="turismo">tourism</string>

    <string name="bienvenido">welcome</string>
    <string name="yo">A creative and talented multimedia producer, SEBASTIAN RESTREPO PALACIO captivates with his skills in almost any type of multimedia subject matter. His mastery of various tools and technologies makes him an innovative leader in the field of multimedia production.</string>
    <string name="contacto">contact: </string>
    <string name="telefonos"> phone: </string>
    <string name="plato">recommended dish: </string>
    <string name="name">NAME: </string>
    <string name="comentario">COMMENT: </string>

</resources>